<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

    

    <title>LineBreak</title>
    <generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll v2.5.1</generator>
		<icon>http://line-break.github.io/apple-touch-icon-precomposed.png</icon>
    <subtitle>Every new line has a purpose</subtitle>
    <link href="http://line-break.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="http://line-break.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <updated>2015-01-04T20:51:11-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://line-break.github.io/</id>
    <author>
			<name>Stephen Lu</name>
			<uri>http://line-break.github.io/</uri>
			<email>munk801@gmail.com</email>
		</author>

    
    <entry>
        <title>Time for Change</title>
        <link href="http://line-break.github.io/time-for-change/"/>
        <updated>2014-01-02T23:22:17-08:00</updated>
        <id>http://line-break.github.io/time-for-change</id>
        <author>
					<name>Stephen Lu</name>
					<uri>http://line-break.github.io/</uri>
					<email>munk801@gmail.com</email>
				</author>
        <content type="html">
        	&lt;img src=&quot;http://line-break.github.io/images/LineBreak_feature.png&quot;&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        	&lt;p&gt;This is the beginning of a new year.  Everybody likes to take this time to make resolutions for the year.
While this is great for people to reinvigorate their lifes goals, it is also a endless loop for a lot of people.
One big loop that people fall into is telling themselves things will be different when they put themselves on
repeat the year after.  Now rather than creating new years goals, why not reiterate your life goals with
small tangible tasks to reach these goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one big step for us as a group of Linebreak.  We started off coding 29+ hours over a weekend to
get the most of what we can for Startup Weekend Orange County.  What started as a cool event to check out
over a weekend has now turned into a potential opportunity for us to really do something amazing in the
young age of our lives.  We have a chance to really bring something big to our community and to really
bring purpose into our lives as well as the lives of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where Linebreak comes into play.  Linebreak means something so much more to our group now
more than ever.  Linebreak now has a meaning.  Using our passions and knowledge of the everchanging
tech industry and providing a service that can bring this passion and technology to you.  Taking
your ideas for a better world and transforming it into an iterative and tangible product.  Taking
the most up to date features and creating a product that can co-exist in the world with the best
out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I confidently feel that we can provide a tremendous service for providing product development at
a rapid pace and at the highest quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Munk out!&lt;/p&gt;

        </content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>